https://www.cs.columbia.edu/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Toggle navigation
General
Academic Advising
Computing Research Facilities (CRF)
Dual MS in Journalism and Computer Science Program
Doctor of Engineering Science (DES)
ArtificialIntelligence
The Privacy Policy of The Fu Foundation School of Engineering and Applied Science of Columbia University in the City of New York
Thank you for visiting The Fu Foundation School of Engineering and Applied Science Web site(s) and service(s). Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we have developed this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used within our sites and services. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.
When Personal Information Is Collected and How The Fu Foundation School of Engineering and Applied Science Uses Your Personal Information
The Fu Foundation School of Engineering and Applied Science collects personal information to make our site(s) and service(s) more relevant and rewarding for you to use.
For each visitor to our Web pages, our Web server automatically recognizes your domain, service provider, operating system, and internet browser. Our Web server additionally records usage of pages by our visitors. We use this information, in aggregate, for our research reports and performance surveys. We sometimes use this non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience.
Some of The Fu Foundation School of Engineering and Applied Science site(s) and service(s) collect personally identifiable information to further personalize your experience within a site. Some site(s) and service(s) require that you provide personally identifiable information in order to participate in the activities and offerings within.
We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs, or services that we believe may be of interest to you. We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when we make changes to our services, to fulfill a request by you, or to contact you about your account with us. Most of our communications provide an “opt-out” feature.
We may also use your information to update internal systems. This allows for seamless delivery of services and resources to you across the University.
The Fu Foundation School of Engineering and Applied Science Web Site(s) and Service(s) may contain email services, bulletin board services, chat areas, news groups, forums, communities, personal Web pages, calendars, photo displays, and/or other message or communication facilities designed to enable you to communicate with others (collectively, “Communication Services”). The information we collect in connection with these Communication Services is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these Communication Services. Within many of these Communication Services, The Fu Foundation School of Engineering and Applied Science provides you multiple privacy options that allow you to restrict the use and viewability of your information to others.
Cookies
To enhance and personalize your experience, some of our Web pages use “cookies.” Cookies are text files that your Web browser places on your computer’s hard drive to store your preferences. When using cookies, we do not store personally identifiable information within the cookie. For more information about cookies, please visit http://www.cookiecentral.com.
Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites
Some of our site(s) and service(s) contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy policies as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. This site contains third-party tracking code for Google Analytics, which uses cookies to track anonymous data.
Will The Fu Foundation School of Engineering and Applied Science Disclose My Personal Information to Parties Outside the University?
The Fu Foundation School of Engineering and Applied Science does not sell, rent, give away, or loan any identifiable information regarding its members to any third party other than agents and contractors of The Fu Foundation School of Engineering and Applied Science or Columbia University.
Agents and contractors of The Fu Foundation School of Engineering and Applied Science or Columbia University who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this privacy policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for The Fu Foundation School of Engineering and Applied Science or Columbia University.
The Fu Foundation School of Engineering and Applied Science or Columbia University may release personal information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements, or (iii) protect the rights, property, or safety of The Fu Foundation School of Engineering and Applied Science, Columbia University, our users, or others.
How The Fu Foundation School of Engineering and Applied Science Protects Your Information
We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. We secure information transmission, storage, and retrieval.
On our secure server(s), we use industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to guarantee the confidentiality of online transactions made on our site. SSL authentication and encryption of the information that you send to us over the Internet helps protect your online transaction information from third-party interception.
We never display your sensitive information such as your full Social Security number or credit card number once it has been entered. We will only reveal the last four digits of your credit card for verification purposes.
We urge you to protect your own privacy. We recommend that you do not share any account information or passwords used to access our site(s) or service(s). We would never request from your password from you.
Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this privacy policy.
Unfortunately, despite all our efforts, there is always a risk that third parties may unlawfully intercept transmissions. This reality is true of all Internet use. As a result, we cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit, and you transmit all information at your own risk.
How You Can Access or Correct Your Information
Many of the online site(s) and service(s) we provide allow you to manage your personal information. Should you need further assistance, please contact us using the contact information provided below.
To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
How Does The Fu Foundation School of Engineering and Applied Science Protect the Privacy of Children Younger Than 13 Years?
The Fu Foundation School of Engineering and Applied Science is concerned about the privacy of young children and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under 13 years. We suggest that you become involved with your child’s access to the Internet and to our site to ensure that his or her privacy is well protected.
Your Consent
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of your information by The Fu Foundation School of Engineering and Applied Science and Columbia University. The full terms of use are contained within the “Columbia Engineering Web Site(s)/Service(s) Terms of Use” at the following URL: http://engineering.columbia.edu/terms-use.
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, or the content or practices of our Web site, you can contact Columbia University Information Technology:
615 West 131st Street, Mail Code: 8750 New York, NY 10027 websupport@columbia.edu
COVID-19 Response
The Columbia Engineering community has come together to combat the coronavirus pandemic on multiple fronts. In close collabo-ration with the Columbia University Irving Medical Center, we’re leveraging our expertise and innovation to address short term medical needs and long term societal impacts.
Learn more about the COVID-19 Response
Upcoming Events
Dec
11
NLP - Faisal Ladhak
Friday 12:00 pm
Online lecture
Faisal Ladhak, Columbia University
Dec
14
Demystifying the Dissertation - Yuchi Tian
Demystifying the Dissertation: PhD Research Discussions
Monday 11:00 am
https://columbiauniversity.zoom.us/s/91230045928?pwd=cmtqcjQrdjh5VHdNcEp3bWtSNWRCQT09
Yuchi Tian
Dec
14
CS@CU MS Bridge Info Session
Monday 3:00 pm
Online Event
Prof. Tony Dear, https://www.cs.columbia.edu/ms-bridge/
Dec
15
Demystifying the PhD - Elsbeth Turcan
Tuesday 1:00 pm
https://columbiauniversity.zoom.us/s/98163303253?pwd=OXRYdjRSd3NVSmpTeXppdm02SGFJZz09#success
Elsbeth Turcan
View All >>
Around the Department
In the News
Press Mentions
© Columbia
Webmaster
Privacy Policy
This website uses cookies and similar tools and technologies to improve your experience and to help us understand how you use our site. By continuing to use this website, you consent to Columbia University's use of cookies and similar technologies. For more information about Columbia University website cookie policy, please visit our Cookie PolicyOk
Dean Boyce's statement on amicus brief filed by President Bollinger
President Bollinger announced that Columbia University along with many other academic institutions (sixteen, including all Ivy League universities) filed an amicus brief in the U.S. District Court for the Eastern District of New York challenging the Executive Order regarding immigrants from seven designated countries and refugees. Among other things, the brief asserts that “safety and security concerns can be addressed in a manner that is consistent with the values America has always stood for, including the free flow of ideas and people across borders and the welcoming of immigrants to our universities.”
This recent action provides a moment for us to collectively reflect on our community within Columbia Engineering and the importance of our commitment to maintaining an open and welcoming community for all students, faculty, researchers and administrative staff. As a School of Engineering and Applied Science, we are fortunate to attract students and faculty from diverse backgrounds, from across the country, and from around the world. It is a great benefit to be able to gather engineers and scientists of so many different perspectives and talents – all with a commitment to learning, a focus on pushing the frontiers of knowledge and discovery, and with a passion for translating our work to impact humanity.
I am proud of our community, and wish to take this opportunity to reinforce our collective commitment to maintaining an open and collegial environment. We are fortunate to have the privilege to learn from one another, and to study, work, and live together in such a dynamic and vibrant place as Columbia.
Sincerely,
{{#speaker}}Speaker: {{{speaker}}}{{#organization}}, {{organization}}{{/organization}}{{/speaker}}
{{#wwwLink}}{{personal_uri}}{{/wwwLink}} {{#cvLink}}{{cv_uri}}{{/cvLink}} {{#scholarLink}}{{scholar_uri}}{{/scholarLink}}
{{title}} ({{dept}} {{prefix}}{{course_num}}-{{section}})
{{/courses}}
{{/showCourses}}
{{#showBlogs}}{{{blog_posts}}}{{/showBlogs}}
Close
